(Leonard:)Well, maybe not, but some
day we actually will be old,
(Leonard:)and we'll look
back on this night
(Leonard:)and remember what
a good time we had.
(Penny:)Okay, like what?
I know. Food fight!
(Leonard:)I'll keep thinking.
(Amy:)Look, I know you both feel bad
about being alone, but sometimes
(Amy:)the best thing you can do is
take a little time for yourself,
(Amy:)especially when you just
got out of a relationship.
(Sheldon:)Speaking of ending
relationships,
(Sheldon:)when British Honduras
became Belize,
(Sheldon:)they designed a new
flag with a tree on it,
(Sheldon:)and I would like to hang
myself from that tree.
(Raj:)But, Amy,
when you and Sheldon split up,
(Raj:)didn't you start dating someone
right away?
(Amy:)Well, I... I wouldn't
say right away.
(Sheldon:)And actually, it was
three different men.